Interviewer: What are you doing in the US?
Cara: I’m visiting from England.
I’m just on holiday for one week.
Interviewer: Was there anything that surprised you about the US when you arrived?
Cara: Um, I was quite surprised by how busy New York is.
Although I suppose I shouldn’t have been because it’s one of the biggest cities.
Um, and there are lots of nice places to eat as well.
Interviewer: How do people in your country drive?
Madeleine: I think it depends where you are.
Where I live in Oregon, everything is very safe, much slower,
but in New York City everything is very fast, very dangerous.
Interviewer: Are you a typical driver for where you live for Oregon?
Madeleine: I would say so, I drive, I’m a very cautious driver.
Interviewer: Do you have any ambitions for this year?
Chris: Um, yes, I’d like to visit my daughter in Australia, and also plan towards my retirement.
Interviewer: Do you think you’re going to do them?
Chris: Certainly the planning, whether or not I achieve the visit is something else.
Interviewer: Have you ever seen a movie more than three times?
Susan: I’ve seen Casablanca many times, and I still think it’s one of the best films made.
Interviewer: What do you like about it?
Susan: Everything. I like the direction, the lighting.
I like each of the stars.
The story has romance and intrigue.
I like stories about World War II.
Um, I love Claude Raines, Humphrey Bogart.
There’s like nothing not to like in that movie.
Interviewer: What phone do you have?
Martin: I have an iPhone.
Interviewer: How old is it?
Martin: I believe, I believe my iPhone is now two years old.
Interviewer: How often do you change phones?
Martin: I change phones maybe every three years.
Interviewer: What do you use it for the most?
Martin: I mostly use my phone for social media.